Guide to the Records of the Office of the President (Oliva) RG.3.0.11
New York University Archives
- Series II. Writing and Speeches, 1963-2002; 21.2 Linear Feet in 48 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  - Subseries II.B Speeches, 1984-2002
    - Metro International Fulbright Dinner (Oliva Honored), May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Haskins Partners Dinner (Oliva Honored), May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Give a Violet Reception, May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Stern School Undergraduate Pre-Commencement, May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Salute to Class of 1997, May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - College of Arts and Sciences Baccalaureate Ceremony, May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Commencement, May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
    - Commencement Anniversary Alumni Reception, May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - School of Medicine Last Day Exercises, May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - School of Law Convocation, May 1997 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Resource Network Dinner, June 1997 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - School of Continuing Education 19th International Hospitality Investment Conference, June 1997 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - School of Dentistry Graduation, June 1997 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Association Dinner, June 1997 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Administrative Management Council Dinner, June 1997 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Distinguished Administrator Award Dinner (Oliva Honored), June 1997 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Park Enforcement Patrol for Washington Square Park Press Conference, August 1997 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - President's Picnic, September 1997 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - New Faculty Introduction, September 1997 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Council Reception, September 1997 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Memorial Service for Ed Diamond, September 1997 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Dinner Honoring Martin Gruber, September 1997 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion Convocation, September 1997 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Welcome Back Dinner for Vice Presidents and Deans, September 1997 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Dinner Honoring Alice Huang, September 1997 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Reception for Richard Maass and Maass Collection Dedication, September 1997 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Luncheon to Welcome Dean Boufford, September 1997 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Law School Induction Dinner and Dedication of Martin Lipton Hall, October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars and Opportunity Fellows Reception, October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - School of Continuing Education Preston Robert Tisch Award for Distinguished Industry Leadership, October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Cantor Film Center Dedication, October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Reception for Yari Yari Conference, "Black Women Writers and the Future: An International Conference on Literature by Women of African Descent", October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Varsity Club Hall of Fame Dinner, October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Stern School Centennial Campaign Kick-off, October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - School of Law Dinner with Supreme Court Justices, October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Reception Honoring Stephen Brown, October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Parents' Weekend President's Reception and School Visits, October 1997 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Dean Daly's Class, November 1997 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Dinner Honoring Arthur Shorin, November 1997 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Development and Alumni Relations Conference, November 1997 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Resource Network President's Dinner, November 1997 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Morning at Washington Square, November 1997 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - 12th Alumni Finance Forum -- "Investment Strategies for 1998", November 1997 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Celebration of 10th Anniversary of Neural Science at NYU, November 1997 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Resource Network Senior Officers Reception, November 1997 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Dinner for Maurice S. Kanbar, November 1997 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - "Facing the Jobs Challenge" Luncheon, December 1997 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Asian/Pacific/American Studies Program and Institute Dinner, December 1997 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Black Community Crusade for Children Check Presentation, December 1997 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Guidance Counselor Reception, December 1997 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Johns Hopkins University Alumni Basketball Reception, December 1997 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Dinner Honoring Maurice R. Greenberg and Presentation of Presidential Medal, December 1997 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - President's Holiday Party for Student Leaders, December 1997 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Sir Harold Acton Award Lecture and Dinner, December 1997 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - University of Rochester Alumni Basketball Reception, January 1998 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Emory University UAA Alumni Reception, January 1998 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Carnegie Mellon University UAA Alumni Reception, January 1998 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Jules Martin Reception, January 1998 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Admissions Office Thank You Reception, February 1998 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Texaco Luncheon, February 1998 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Center for Ancient Studies Dinner, February 1998 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Citizens Committee for New York City New Yorker for New York Awards Dinner, February 1998 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Amsterdam Breakfast -- Agreement between NYU and University of Amsterdam, February 1998 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - University of Chicago UAA Alumni Reception, February 1998 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Washington University in St. Louis UAA Alumni Reception, February 1998 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Mount Sinai-NYU Medical Center Establishment Reception, February 1998 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - NYU in Albany Day Alumni Reception, February 1998 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Rita and Burton Goldberg Theatre Dedication and Reception, February 1998 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - America Reads Launch, March 1998 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Memorial Service for Annette Weiner, March 1998 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Lewis Rudin Scholarship Reception, March 1998 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 1998 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - NYU Health Center Opening Reception, March 1998 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner, March 1998 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Rudolph F. Crew, March 1998 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Times Square/42nd Street Redevelopment Breakfast, March 1998 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Washington, D.C. Alumni Reception, March 1998 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Ford Foundation Career Roundtable, April 1998 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Reception Honoring Richard J. Koppenaal, April 1998 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Conference on Urban Issues -- "The Challenges and Opportunities of Globalization for Cities in Spain, Latin America, and the United States", April 1998 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Saturday at the Square, April 1998 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - President's Service Awards, April 1998 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Presidential Lecture with Michael Gibson -- "Botanizing in the Asphalt? Being Lost in Middle Eastern Cities", April 1998 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Luncheon for Alan Menken, April 1998 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Kriser Family Reception, April 1998 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Founder's Day Honors Convocation, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Luncheon for Senator Jack Reed, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Student Athlete Academic Achievement Awards, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - President's Reception for Graduating Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Caring Community Breakfast, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Dean John Sexton 10th Anniversary Dinner, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Give a Violet Reception, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - National Scholarship Finalists Reception, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Irving H. Jurow Lecture by David Halberstam and Reception, April 1998 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - 25-Year Service Awards Breakfast, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Service Recognition Reception, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Association of Black Faculty, Administrators and Staff Luncheon and Award Ceremony, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - $24 Award Reception for E. L. Doctorow, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Chubb/NYU Scholarship and Internship Program Breakfast, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Haskins Partners Dinner, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Provincetown Playhouse Dedication, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Memorial Service for Bluma Trell, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - School of Education Doctoral Convocation, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Stern School Undergraduate Pre-Commencement, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Salute to the Graduating Class of 1998, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - College of Arts and Sciences Baccalaureate Ceremony, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Commencement, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Medical School Last Day Exercises, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Distinguished Administrator Award Dinner, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Edward G. Kaufman Retirement Dinner, May 1998 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Dinner for Father McGuire on 25th Ordination Anniversary, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Hospitality Industry Investment Conference, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - America Reads Reception, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Dental School Commencement, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Management Council End of the Year Dinner, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement Awards Ceremony, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Association Annual Awards Dinner, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Rudin Awards, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Jack Brause Library Reception, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Edward G. Kaufman Retirement Dinner, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Protection Services Awards, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Prague Dinner, June 1998 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Dean's Council Dinner, July 1998 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - President's Picnic, September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - New Faculty Introduction, September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - President's Recognition Reception for Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars, September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Council Reception, September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Wagner Labor Archives Reception, September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Legends of the Village Awards, September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Maya Lin Reception for Exhibition Opening, September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Law School Forum -- "Strengthening Democracy in the Global Economy", September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Africana Studies Reception, September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Luncheon for President Rafael Caldera of Venezuela, September 1998 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Reception for Fellows, October 1998 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Dinner Honoring Danny Glover, October 1998 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Rudin Scholarship Reception, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Varsity Club Hall of Fame Dinner, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Heights Overlook Dedication, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - School of Continuing Education -- Celebration of Name Change to School of Continuing and Professional Studies, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Danny Glover, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Alumni Reception, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Los Angeles Alumni Reception, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Parents' Weekend President's Reception, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Roundtable Discussion of University Presidents on Public and Private Partnerships in Higher Education, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Zerilli-Marimò Prize for Italian Fiction, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Model Employers Awards Breakfast, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - School of Medicine Welcome Reception for Robert M. Glickman, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Glucksman Ireland House 5th Anniversary Events, October 1998 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Tiro A. Segno Foundation Ball, November 1998 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Finance Forum, November 1998 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Society of the Torch Luncheon, November 1998 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Lecture by and Dinner for Dr. Claire Fagin, November 1998 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Morning at Washington Square, November 1998 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Romare Bearden Symposium, November 1998 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Luncheon Honoring Donald R. Greene, November 1998 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - School of Continuing and Professional Studies Preston Robert Tisch Award Dinner, November 1998 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Faculty Resource Network Liaison Officers Reception, November 1998 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Sokol Faculty Award in the Sciences, November 1998 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Child Study Center Child Advocacy Award Dinner, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Guidance Counselor Reception, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Alan Hevesi, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - John Brown Breakfast at the Regency, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Metro Center Torch of Learning Award, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Rudin Dedication, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - An Evening Honoring Noel L. Cohen, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Holiday Party for Student Leaders, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Full Faculty Council Luncheon, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Videoconference with University of Florence, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - The Global Connection Conference -- "The Global Connection: Investment, Trade, Culture, and Tourism", December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Memorial Service for Jerry Berkowitz, December 1998 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Reception Honoring Carol Mandel, January 1999 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Reception Honoring Ralph Minasian, January 1999 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Acton Medalists' Dinner, January 1999 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Sir Harold Acton Lecture and Dinner, February 1999 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Lillian Vernon Center for International Affairs Dedication and Dinner, February 1999 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - League of World Universities Conference, February 1999 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Dinner Honoring Wole Soyinka, February 1999 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - NYU in Albany Day Reception, February 1999 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with John W. Rowe, March 1999 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 1999 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - University Hall Dedication, March 1999 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Full Faculty Council Luncheon, March 1999 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Gala Honoring Laurence A. Tisch, March 1999 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner, March 1999 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Reception for Keiko Ibi, March 1999 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - National Scholarship Finalists Reception, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - President's Service Awards, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Saturday at the Square, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Washington, D. C. Alumni Reception, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Kriser Family Reception, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Founders Day Luncheon with Andrew M. Cuomo, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Student Athlete Academic Achievement Awards, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Dedication of Jewel Zelensky Lounge, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Dedication of Henry Kaufman Management Education Center, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Reception for Graduating Seniors, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Dinner Honoring David Baltimore, April 1999 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Law School Campaign Dinner, April 1999 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Office for African American, Latino and Asian American Student Services (OASIS) 10th Anniversary Awards Celebration, April 1999 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Give a Violet Reception, April 1999 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Chubb/NYU Scholarship and Internship Program Breakfast, April 1999 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Admissions Office Thank-You Reception, April 1999 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Farewell Reception for Dean Carlton Rochell, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Women in Financial Development Luncheon Honoring Naomi Levine, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - ABFAS Luncheon and Award Ceremony, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Eleanore Korman Retirement Reception, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - 25 Year Service Awards Breakfast, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Haskins Partners Dinner, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Service Recognition Reception, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - First Annual Varsity Student Athlete Banquet, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Stern School Pre-Commencement, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Salute, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Gallatin School Commencement, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Commencement, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Medical School Commencement, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Events at Villa La Pietra: Acton Awards, Concert, and Lecture, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - C-Team Auction Cabaret, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Dinner Celebrating Opening of "When Time Began to Rant and Rage" at the Grey Art Gallery, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Reception Honoring Ray Lumpp, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Reception Honoring Matilda Raffa Cuomo, May 1999 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Administrative Management Council End of Year Reception and Dinner, June 1999 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Dental School Graduation, June 1999 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Thank You Reception, June 1999 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Alumni Association Awards Dinner, June 1999 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - International Hospitality Industry Investment Conference, June 1999 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - International Hospitality Industry Investment Conference Breakfast, June 1999 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Susan D. Hibbard Scholarship Ceremony, June 1999 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Center for Advanced Technology (CAT) Ultraviolet 99, June 1999 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Protection Services Awards Ceremony, June 1999 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Medical School Installation of Robert M. Glickman as Dean, June 1999 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Dinner Honoring Gerald Heeger, June 1999 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - General Studies Program, Villa La Pietra -- Parents' Welcome Reception, August 1999 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - New Faculty Reception, September 1999 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Reception, September 1999 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Gala Benefit to Honor Juan Villalonga, September 1999 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Founders Society Dinner Cruise, September 1999 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Conference to Honor Samuel J. Williamson, September 1999 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Lax and Nirenberg Reception, September 1999 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - NYU Celebrates 2000, October 1999 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Varsity Club Athletics Hall of Fame Dinner, October 1999 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Torch Club Opening Reception, October 1999 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Hitchcock Conference Dinner, October 1999 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Peter Vallone, October 1999 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Stern School Centennial Celebration Kickoff, October 1999 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Parents' Weekend President's Reception, October 1999 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Named Professorships Reception, October 1999 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Center for the Neuroscience of Fear and Anxiety Inaugural Reception, November 1999 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Association Finance Forum, November 1999 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Pre-Millennium Salute to Musical Theatre, November 1999 (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
    - Faculty Resource Network Dinner, November 1999 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Morning at Washington Square, November 1999 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Acton Award Dinner, November 1999 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Events at Villa La Pietra, November 1999 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Lew Rudin Scholarship Reception, November 1999 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Association Great Teacher Lecture, November 1999 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Ian Smith, December 1999 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Holiday Party for Student Leaders, December 1999 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Full Faculty Council Luncheon, December 1999 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - 14th Street-Union Square Local Development Corporation and Business Improvement District Reception, December 1999 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - IIE/German Academic Exchange Service (DAAD) Reception, January 2000 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Council Reception, January 2000 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Association Student Leaders Dinner, January 2000 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - "Memories of the World to Come: New York and Buenos Aires 1910-2010", February 2000 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - School of Continuing and Professional Studies Preston Robert Tisch Award, February 2000 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Brokaw Dinner, February 2000 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Events in Palm Beach, February 2000 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 2000 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Awards, March 2000 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Washington, D. C. Alumni Reception, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Center for French Civilization and Culture Dinner, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Memorial Service for Daniel E. Griffiths, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Saturday at the Square, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Seniors Reception, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Rhodes Dinner, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Caring Community Breakfast, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Kriser Family Reception, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Statement in Support of Petition for Tax Exempt Status for Buenos Aires, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Morning on the Millennium with Stephen Jay Gould, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Founder's Day, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Student Athlete Academic Achievement Awards, April 2000 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - President's Service Awards, April 2000 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Give a Violet Reception, April 2000 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - NYU Alumnae Club Jubilee Scholarship and Key Pin Awards Celebration, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - ABFAS Luncheon and Award Ceremony, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - 25-Year Service Awards, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Russian History Roundtable, "Putin's Russia: Historical and Contemporary Perspectives", May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Distinguished Administrator Awards, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - National Scholarship Finalists, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Varsity Student Athlete Dinner, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - School of Contuining Education Baccalaureate Ceremonies, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Stern School Pre-Commencement, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Tisch School of the Arts Salute, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Commencement, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - School of Medicine Convocation, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - American Consulate Report, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Ferragamo Luncheon, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Sir Harold Acton Lecture and Dinner -- Villa La Pietra, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 17)